[
	{
		"question": "What did Tango name his and Jimmy's Warden in Double Life?",
		"answers": ["Rancher's Revenge", "Rancher's Wrath", "Rancher's Bodyguard", "It didn't have a name"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Why did Ren begin wearing a crown in Third Life?",
		"answers": ["To show off his MCC win", "Got it in a box of cereal", "To make Dogwarts into a kingdom", "Carried over from Hermitcraft"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the name of Grian's Magma cube? ",
		"answers": ["Etho's Fridge", "Etho's Oven", "Etho's Dishwasher", "Etho's Microwave"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the color of Skizz's underwear in Limited Life?",
		"answers": ["Red", "Yellow", "Green", "White with hearts"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "How was the Double Life Warden killed?",
		"answers": ["Bow and arrow", "Fishing rod", "Sword", "Axe"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Who killed the Ender Dragon in Secret Life?",
		"answers": ["Scott", "Impulse", "Pearl", "Bdubs"],
		"correct_answer_index": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "BigB has an alternate ego that he uses throughout the series. What is his name? ",
		"answers": ["Cherry", "Berry", "Terry", "Jerry"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Which one of these hasn't been a feature in Bdubs' skin during the Life Series?",
		"answers": ["A golden tooth", "A red bandana", "A black eye", "A missing tooth"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "In Third Life, how did Martyn kill Ren to turn him red?",
		"answers": ["With an axe", "With TNT", "With a sword", "Shoved him off a cliff"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Who won \"You Bet Your Life\" in Last Life?",
		"answers": ["Cleo", "Scott", "Joel", "Lizzie"],
		"correct_answer_index": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Which players weren't pressent for the trapdoor sleepover in Secret Life?",
		"answers": ["Martyn and Etho", "Etho and Tango", "Grian and Etho", "Martyn and Grian"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What did Scar and Pearl use to hurt their soulmates in Double Life?",
		"answers": ["Lava", "Gravel/sand", "Powdered snow", "Drowning"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was referred to as the \"Red King\" in Third Life?",
		"answers": ["Martyn", "Scar", "Ren", "Bdubs"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "When did Gem make her first appearance in the Life Series?",
		"answers": ["Wild Life", "Secret Life", "Limited Life", "Real Life"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the name of Pearl's cat in Limited Life?",
		"answers": ["Froggy", "Tilly", "Jumpy", "Hoppy"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the cause of Lizzie's final death in Secret Life?",
		"answers": ["Drowning", "An Enderman", "Fell into the void", "Fall damage"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Which goat horn type did Jimmy and Tango have in Double Life?",
		"answers": ["Ponder", "Sing", "Dream", "Seek"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "How many times did Skizz die in the first episode of Limited Life? ",
		"answers": ["4 times", "3 times", "2 times", "5 times"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the first to fail a task in Secret Life?",
		"answers": ["Mumbo", "Jimmy", "Skizz", "Scar"],
		"correct_answer_index": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the name of Scott and Pearl's base in Last Life? ",
		"answers": ["Scottagecore", "The Mosscottage", "Home Sweet Home", "The Scottage"],
		"correct_answer_index": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Who opened the End portal in Secret Life? ",
		"answers": ["Gem", "Pearl", "Impulse", "Bdubs"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Who were the wizards in Last Life?",
		"answers": ["Scott and Pearl", "Bdubs and Etho", "Joel and Lizzie", "Scar and Joel"],
		"correct_answer_index": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Who started the zombie curse in Secret Life session 7?",
		"answers": ["Cleo", "Bdubs", "Gem", "Martyn"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "What block was Etho's swamp fortress primarily made out of in Third Life?",
		"answers": ["Leaves", "Spruce", "Wool", "Dark oak"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Who betrayed Cleo in Last Life? ",
		"answers": ["Scott", "Lizzie", "BigB", "Ren"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Who had a wolf pack in Third Life? ",
		"answers": ["Scar", "Grian", "Joel", "Pearl"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "On what mob did Gem and Pearl ride around killing people together?",
		"answers": ["Horse", "Skeleton horse", "Pig", "Camel"],
		"correct_answer_index": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the first ever Boogeyman in the Life Series?",
		"answers": ["Etho", "Bdubs", "Grian", "Scott"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Who pranked other players with light grey stained glass in Third Life?",
		"answers": ["Etho", "Impulse", "Tango", "Bdubs"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the name of Scar's base in Secret Life?",
		"answers": ["Saloon Scar", "Scar's Outpost", "Trader Scar's", "Scar's Emporium"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "In Limited Life, Pearl and BigB decorated their tower with the face of an animal. What was it?",
		"answers": ["Frogs", "Wolves", "Sheep", "Cats"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Who built the Ghast farm in Last Life?",
		"answers": ["Etho and Grian", "Impulse and Tango", "Grian and Mumbo", "Impulse and Mumbo"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Who did Mumbo compete against to have the biggest tower in Secret Life?",
		"answers": ["Grian", "Gem", "Pearl", "Joel"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the S in team BEST?",
		"answers": ["Scott", "Scar", "Skizz", "Sgrian"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Between Bdubs, Impulse, Tango, and Scott, who was out first during Tag in Secret Life?",
		"answers": ["Impulse", "Tango", "Bdubs", "Scott"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Who threw a birthday party in Limited Life?",
		"answers": ["Jimmy", "Martyn", "Joel", "Scott"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What was Lizzie's base in Secret Life?",
		"answers": ["Giant peach", "Giant watermelon", "Giant apple", "Giant pumpkin"],
		"correct_answer_index": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Which team blew up Bread Bridge in Limited Life? ",
		"answers": ["Clockers", "Nosey Neighbots", "TIES", "Mean Gills"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	}
]